radeon.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy

​Last revised October 2016

Advanced Micro Devices, Inc. Privacy Policy. 

This website (the “Site”) is operated in the United States of America by Advanced Micro Devices, Inc. (“AMD”, “We”, “Our” or “Us”), a company incorporated in the state of Delaware, United States, in 1969. Advanced Micro Devices, Inc.’s headquarters is located at 1 AMD Place, PO Box 3453 Sunnyvale, CA 94088-3453. This Privacy Policy applies to personal information which is collected and used by Advanced Micro Devices, Inc., which includes all companies in the AMD group of companies (together “AMD”, “We”, “Our” or “Us”). This Privacy Policy forms part of the Site’s Terms and Conditions of Use and describes how We collect, protect and use the personal information We receive from visitors to the Site. 

### Personal Information We collect

We collect several kinds of information from you, depending on the part of the Site being visited. For example, We collect personal information from you when you register for a forum or newsletter, download products such as drivers, register products with Us, create a user name and password, provide feedback, send email enquiries or participate in another part of the Site.

The information that We collect is set out on the relevant pages of the Site and may include your name, email address, postal address, postcode, country of residence, job title, daytime and/or mobile phone number and information about your workplace and the nature of your business. If you use the Site to apply for jobs at AMD We will also collect information about your educational background and employment history and We will request your professional resume/CV. 

In general, you can visit the Site without revealing any information about yourself. However, if you choose not to register on the Site you may not be able to use its features to their fullest extent. For example, you will not be able to participate in forum discussions on the Site. 

### Our use of your information

We may use the personal information We collect via the Site for any of the following purposes:

  * providing, developing, improving and personalising Our services and the Site; 
  * registering you on the Site; 
  * providing you (subject to the **Direct Marketing** section below) with marketing communications; 
  * dealing with your inquiries and requests; 
  * generating anonymous reports about use of the Site and its features; 
  * allowing you to take part in competitions, campaigns, promotions or surveys;
  * keeping you up to date by sending you Our newsletters; and 
  * considering you for employment if you have provided personal information pursuant to an application for a job with AMD. 

### Direct Marketing

We may use your personal information to provide you with marketing communications, such as newsletters or information about Our products and services, new launches, promotions and special offers.

We may send you such communications by:

  * Email; 
  * SMS text message and/or any other form of electronic message;
  * Push notifications; and
  * any other medium which becomes relevant from time to time. 

You can opt-out of receiving communications from AMD at any time by writing to the AMD Communication Preference Centre at memberservices@amd-member.com or by following the unsubscribe instructions set out in each of our communications to you. You may also opt-out by contacting us at [memberservices@amd-member.com](mailto:memberservices@amd-member.com). However, We may still need to contact you in the event of a change to our Terms and Conditions, Privacy Policy, Cookie Policy or concerning an account you may have with us.

### Disclosure of Information

We will not disclose your personal information that We collect from the Site to any third parties without your consent except:

  * to employees and independent contractors of AMD, analytic vendors, and other service providers and suppliers if the disclosure will enable that party to perform a business, professional, or technical support function for AMD or to perform a service that you have requested; 
  * to and between companies within the AMD group; 
  * where you give Us permission to disclose your personal information to third parties selected by Us for marketing purposes; 
  * if We are required to do so to comply with a legal requirement or request from a competent court, regulator or other authority; 
  * where We deem it necessary, in Our sole discretion, to protect Our legal rights or property or the legal rights or property of an individual who registers with the Site or any third party, or to prevent personal injury; and/or 
  * in connection with a sale, merger, assignment, joint venture or other transfer or disposition of a portion or all of Our assets or stock or Our affiliated entities (including, without limitation, in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings). 

We will take reasonable steps to ensure that any personal information about you that We pass to a third party will be held securely by that party and only be used for the purposes for which it was provided to them. Except as noted above, information We collect from Site visitors will not be shared with individuals or other companies unrelated to, or that do not perform a business, professional or technical function for AMD.

### Security and Quality

AMD is committed to taking reasonable steps to protect the personal information that you provide. We use a variety of advanced security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, We store the personal information you provide on secured computer servers that are located in controlled facilities. Additionally, when We transmit sensitive personal information over the Internet, We protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. Please help Us to keep your personal information secure by not using an obvious login name or password and ensuring you do not divulge your password to any other person.

The personal information that We collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"), in particular the United States and Hong Kong. It may also be processed by individuals operating outside the EEA who work for Us or for one of our suppliers. Such individuals may be engaged in, among other things, the processing of your personal information for the provision of Our services and/or products, marketing purposes (subject to the Direct Marketing section above) and for customer relationship management purposes. By submitting your personal information, you agree to this transfer, storing and processing.

We do our best to maintain the accuracy of any personal information you do supply to Us. You can help AMD update and maintain the accuracy of any personal information you supply by notifying AMD of any changes to your address, title, phone number or e-mail address. In some parts of the Site, you may do this online by following the instructions on membership profile pages. You may also do this by contacting the address set out in the Access to your information section of this Privacy Policy. Although We make every effort to create a secure environment for your personal information, We cannot guarantee the safety of any personal information you transmit to us online.

### AMD’s Cookie Policy

  * AMD’s Cookie Policy is available for review here.

### Links to external websites

The Site contains links to other websites belonging to third parties. These websites are not covered by this Privacy Policy and We are not responsible for the privacy practices within any of these other websites. You should be aware of this when you leave the Site and We encourage you to read the privacy statements of other websites.

### Access to your information

You have the right to request a copy of the personal information We hold about you and to have any inaccuracies corrected. Please address requests (with a return email where possible) to:

AMD Communication Preference Centre  

Or by Post to:  
AMD Web Services Team  
1 Commerce Valley Dr. East  
Markham, ON L3T 7X6  
Canada

### Changes, Oversight and Questions

AMD welcomes comments and questions on this Privacy Policy. We are dedicated to protecting your privacy and will make every reasonable effort to keep your information secure. Due to the rapidly evolving changes on the Internet, We may update this policy. All revisions will be posted to the Site. Regularly viewing this Privacy Policy ensures that you are always aware of what information We collect, how We use it and under what circumstances We will share it with third parties. If you do not agree to the changes We make please do not continue to use the Site.

Comments and questions regarding our policy should be directed to the _Communication Preference Centre_.
